Moving into the fourth bend,
進入第四彎道
in the third place is Satono Diamond.
第三名是里見光鑽
And in the fourth place is Celeste.
第四名是尊貴美德
In the final stretch,
進入最後直線了
Ivory Tower defends her second place
內側是象牙之塔
in the inside line.
死守著第二名的位置
Satono Diamond rushes out from the side.
里見光鑽從外側衝出來了
Go, Diamond!
衝啊 光鑽
Diamond picks up her speed.
里見光鑽從外側進攻
200 meters left.
剩下200公尺
She leaves her opponents behind her
不斷跟拉開差距 領先了一個馬身
and charges forward.
衝出來了 里見光鑽
Go!
衝過終點
The Satono family has finally produced a winner!
里見家的新女主角誕生
Way to go!
跑得不錯嘛
Satono Diamond
里見光鑽
won her debut race.
出色地在新馬出道賽中取得勝利
The last sprint was beautiful.
最後的衝刺實在是太漂亮了
I can't wait to see her future performance.
非常令人期待她今後的表現呢
Looking back, this year has many, many memorable moments.
好的 今年在眾多的比賽裡 也出現了無數名場面
Next week, the voting phase of Arima Kinen will begin.
但就在下週 有馬紀念的粉絲投票就要開始了
Mr. Yamamoto,
山本先生
who do you think we'll see this year?
您覺得今年會是哪些選手會出賽呢
The popular candidates are Bravo Day, who won Tenno Sho,
感覺奪下秋季天皇賞的 讚嘆之日
and Kitasan Black, who won Kikuka Sho.
還有贏下菊花賞的北部玄駒 會是人氣人選吧
However, Gold Ship,
還有過去三度出賽有馬紀念
who has performed very well in three races,
並留下了好成績
and has six victories so far in G1,
現在是GI6勝的黃金船
is noteworthy too.
她也很值得注意
Speaking of Gold Ship,
提到了黃金船
I am reminded of her sudden burst in Takarazuka Kinen.
最令人印象深刻的 就是她在寶塚紀念的衝擊事蹟
That's right.
是啊
She frequently brings surprises to the table in the race.
常常讓比賽出現驚人發展 就是她的魅力所在
I can't wait to see her performance
這是第四度的有馬紀念
in the fourth Arima Kinen.
一起期待她會讓我們 看見什麼樣的比賽吧
UMA MUSUME PRETTY DERBY SEASON 3
《賽馬娘 Pretty Derby 第三季》
So,
(第3話 夢想不會結束) 那麼
let's celebrate Diamond's great debut
讓我們來敬光鑽的新馬出道賽
and her first victory.
(第3話 夢想不會結束) 以及她的首次勝利
Cheers!
乾杯
"SATONO CROWN, CHEVAL GRAND" We have done this many times already.
(里見皇冠 高尚駿逸) 真是的 這是第幾次乾杯了
Why am I here?
為什麼連我也要來
There can never be enough toasts.
因為慶祝幾次都不嫌多啊
Let's invite today's star, Diamond, to say something.
那麼請今天的主角光鑽 來發表一下感想
I managed to make a successful debut today.
終於能在今天得新馬出道賽中 站上了起跑線
Thank you everyone for your support.
謝謝各位為我加油打氣
Then,
那麼…
what is your dream?
今後的抱負是什麼呢
Dream?
抱負
Yes.
對
I'm aiming for next year's Classic Triple Crown.
我的目標 是明年的經典三冠賽
First, it'll be Satsuki Sho.
首先要贏下皐月賞
I will achieve my family's dream.
我一定要實現里見家的GI夙願
Let's work hard together, Diamond.
一起加油吧 光鑽
For our family.
為了里見家的勝利
Now,
那麼…
let's ask Cheval the same question.
接著請小高說說自己的抱負吧
Me?
我也要說嗎
Yes.
是啊
It's a shame that I couldn't take part
我因為初春時的傷勢
in the races this spring due to my injury.
使得無法參加經典賽讓我很不甘心
But I'll do it next year.
所以明年我要捲土重來
I will win G1.
一定要贏下GI
What about your dream?
接下是妳的抱負了
My dream?
我的嗎
Speak now.
來 快說
Uhm...
那個…
Arima Kinen.
是有馬紀念
I want to take part in Arima Kinen.
我的抱負 是參加一直憧憬的有馬紀念
Arima Kinen...
有馬紀念…
But you're already in it.
妳不是已經能參加了嗎
Mhm. You won Kikuka Sho.
是啊 妳都贏下菊花賞了
Oh?
這樣啊
Can I run in the race?
我能夠參賽嗎
Is it a yes?
要是能就好了
Yes.
一定沒有問題的
Diamond.
光鑽
All right.
好
For us and our future.
敬未來的我們
Cheers!
乾杯
Again?
又乾杯
Yay!
太好了
So I can run, right?
所以我可以參加了對吧
Arima Kinen?
有馬紀念
I'm not sure yet,
雖然還沒有確定
but judging from the date
但是不論是從間隔或是距離
and your performance in Kikuka Sho, I'd say yes.
還有妳在菊花賞中的表現來看 妳完全可以應付這場比賽
Hooray!
太好了
You have been racing against your peers.
妳一直以來 都是和同年代的選手在比賽
But in Arima Kinen,
但在有馬紀念裡
you will be pinned against the veterans.
妳將要與身心都經過淬鍊 的高階選手交手
Are you ready?
妳準備好了嗎
Yes!
是
Congratulations, Kita.
恭喜妳 小北
Nice one.
好厲害
Well done.
真有一套
You can do this, Kita.
妳要加油喔 小北
Teio...
帝皇…
Guys...
各位…
I will do my best.
是 我會加油的
What's going on?
怎…怎麼了
This is way over the top.
這也太誇張了吧
Yeah.
很誇張呢
What are you doing?
喂 妳在做什麼
I had difficulties exiting the starting gate.
我有點無法順利從閘門出來
Please.
拜託一下好不好
I don't want a repeat of what happened in Takarazuka Kinen.
我可不想再重現寶塚紀念的惡夢了
It was a great mistake.
畢竟犯了個大錯嘛
It was.
的確是個大錯
We finally passed the re-inspection of the starting gate.
好不容易才通過了閘馬的再審查
If we screw things up in Japan Cup...
要是在這次的日本盃再搞砸的話…
Don't worry.
放心吧
I will get off to a perfect start
下次我一定會用完美的起跑
and win my seventh victory.
拿下草地的GI第7勝
Then, I'll join Arima Kinen
再直接去參加有馬紀念
and be the first horse girl to have eight victories in G1.
達成史上的第一位GI8勝
Stop making grand promises
別老是說這種夢話
and start your training then!
好好練習啊妳
Geez.
她還真的是…
She sure is very determined.
她很有幹勁呢 黃金船
I have high expectations of you, Kitasan.
我也很看好妳喔 北部
I am very determined too!
是 我也是幹勁十足
Arima...
有馬…
Arima is my goal.
目標是有馬
All right.
好
I will not lose to anyone.
我不會跑輸任何人的
"JOIN SPICA OR BE BURIED"
(不加入Spica的人 都要抓去埋)
I have heard your Kikuka Concerto.
我聽過妳的菊花協奏曲了
Your melody.
妳的旋律
Nice to meet you, the most elegant Miss Kitasan Black.
妳好啊 美麗的北部玄駒小姐
I am Sounds of Earth.
我是萬籟爭鳴
"SOUNDS OF EARTH"
(萬籟爭鳴)
Right.
是…
Race is but a symphony between the Earth and the horse girls.
比賽是地球與賽馬娘的一場合奏
All horse girls are magnificent musicians.
所有賽馬娘都是偉大的音樂家
Come.
來
Duet with me.
與我共譜美妙的音色吧
Too close. Too close!
妳的臉 妳的臉太近了
Together, we can play
與妳一起的話
the most exquisite tune in Arima.
我們可以成為飛舞在有馬上空 的頂尖演奏家
You're too close to me!
我說太近了啦
Earth!
好了 萬籟
What are you doing?
妳又在搞什麼
Nature.
優秀素質…
Oh. A harmony is about to begin.
真是的 和聲才正要開始呢
I can't wait, Kitasan Black.
我非常期待呢 北部玄駒
We will unite in the orchestra of Arima Kinen.
有馬紀念的交響樂會
Sheesh.
真是的
Sorry, Kita.
抱歉啊 北部
I hope the new student didn't frighten you.
我們的新人嚇到妳了
New student?
你們的新人
Earth is part of the Canopus?
原來萬籟是Canopus的隊員啊
She's eccentric.
她有點怪怪的就是了
But at the same time,
不過 她並不是只有這樣
she is also very fast.
那個孩子很強喔
Maybe she will win in Arima Kinen.
要是參加有馬紀念的話 說不會贏喔
It'll be Canopus's first G1!
將是Canopus的第一個GI
Will you take part in Arima Kinen?
妳也要參加有馬紀念吧
Yes!
是的
Nothing is set in stone now,
雖然還不確定
but the trainer said that I should be able to attend it.
但是訓練師說我應該可以出場
You are excited.
妳很開心嘛
Yes! Because I dream of competing in it.
是的 畢竟是我一直憧憬的比賽
Arima Kinen
有馬紀念
has a special meaning to me.
對我而言 是很特別的比賽
Arima Kinen, huh?
那個比賽嗎…
Nature, you've participated in it before, haven't you?
優秀素質也有參賽過對吧
Yes, though I got third place three years in a row.
是啊 不過連續三年 都是第三名就是了
But yes, Arima Kinen is special to me too.
但是有馬紀念的確很特別呢
That's right.
就是啊
Thank you, Nature.
謝謝妳 優秀素質
Why so sudden?
怎…怎麼突然這麼說
I can participate in Arima Kinen
我之所以能參加有馬紀念
because I won Kikuka Sho.
是因為我贏下了菊花賞
But it's thanks to your encouragement that I won.
多虧了那一天 妳給了我那麼多的建議
You won the race yourself.
實際贏下比賽的人是妳
I didn't do anything.
我什麼也沒做
But...
可是…
Don't fuss about the details.
妳就別再想些有的沒的
Just train for Arima Kinen now.
現在專心去準備有馬紀念吧
If you need a listener, I'll be there.
想要找人商量的話 我會很樂意聽妳說的
Thank you so much,
好的 謝謝妳
Miss Nature.
優秀素質老師
Miss Nature...
居…居然叫我老師
How did I do?
好啊 怎麼樣
It was perfect, wasn't it?
很完美的起跑吧
Yes. It's good.
是啊 這樣就沒有問題了吧
Great!
怎麼樣
Japan Cup will be mine now.
這下子日本盃就是我的囊中之物了
Don't get ahead of yourself now.
真是的 小心大意失荊州啊
Thank you, McQueen.
謝啦 麥昆
Last lap!
這是最後一圈了
You can do it, Kita!
加油 小北
You broke today's record in your final lap.
在最後跑出今天的最佳時間呢
Yay!
太好了
Drink up.
來 請用
Thank you.
謝謝妳
Are you done with your training now?
嗨 妳也結束練習了嗎
Yes.
是的
But I'm going for another lap.
不過我要再去跑一趟
Kita, your bottle!
小北 妳的瓶子
She's still training?
她還要跑嗎
She's on her growth spurt now.
畢竟是成長飛快的時期嘛
The year will come to an end in a month.
再過一個月 今年就要結束了
Have you picked up your Christmas present?
各位的聖誕禮物都決定好了嗎
Done.
好
Thank you, Kita.
謝謝妳啊 小北
Don't mention it.
這些是小意思啦
By the way, I voted for you
對了 我有投票給小北喔
in Arima Kinen.
有馬紀念的投票
Did you?
是…是這樣嗎
Me too.
我也是喔
Here. Take this.
來 這個給妳
I will cheer for you. Good luck.
我會為妳打氣的 妳要加油喔
Thank you!
謝謝妳
FIERCE RACE IN JAPAN CUP
(日本盃大激戰)
OVERTAKE FAILED, GOLD SHIP RANKED 10TH
(大超車失利 黃金船第十名)
Kita, wakey-wakey.
好了 小北 快點起床
I don't want to leave my bed.
好不想離開被窩喔
Today's breakfast is your favourite, carrot rice and banana steak.
聽說早餐是小北最愛的紅蘿蔔飯 和香蕉排喔
I'll eat a boatload of them
好 那今天也要吃飽飽
and train hard!
再來好好練習吧
Eh?
咦
GOLD SHIP PRESS CONFERENCE
(黃金船臨時記者會)
Gold?
黃金船
Thank you for coming here.
感謝今天到場的各位
I am holding this press conference
之所以會召開這場記者會
to make an announcement.
是因為我想要公布 我的一項決定
Announcement?
決定
I, Gold Ship,
本人黃金船
will compete in Dream Trophy
在完成有馬紀念的比賽後
after Arima Kinen.
將要轉去夢之杯聯賽
If you switch to Dream Trophy,
要是轉去夢之杯聯賽的話
you forfeit your qualification in the Twinkle Series.
您就再也無法參加 閃光系列賽的賽事了
Yes.
沒有錯
Arima Kinen will be
我在閃光系列賽中的賽事
my last run
這次的有馬紀念
in the Twinkle Series.
將會是最後一場比賽
"UMA MUSUME PRETTY DERBY SEASON 3" Last run?
《賽馬娘 Pretty Derby 第三季》 最後一場比賽…
Gold.
黃金船
Do you
那個…
mean what you said?
妳說的是真的嗎
About the last run?
最後一場比賽…
Yes.
是啊
First, it was Satsuki Sho. Then, it was Kikuka Sho.
先是皐月賞 再來是菊花賞
When I first raced in Arima Kinen,
我在初次參賽的有馬紀念裡
I could overtake everyone.
也是力壓眾人
I went from the last place
從最後一名一路衝上去
to the first place.
一次解決所有人
That's how I race.
那就是我的跑法
Somehow,
然而…
things changed.
不知從何時開始變了樣
I cannot control my emotions anymore.
無法好好地去壓仰自己的情緒
You've always been like that.
妳不是一直都這樣嗎
-Watch out! -The starting gate becomes an issue.
-危險啊 -衝出閘門也變得很不擅長
I begin to lose focus.
在很多事上都無法集中精神
Which tile should I play?
該打哪張才好
You've always been like that...
這也一直都是這樣啊
Huh?
什麼
So yeah, I'm serious about my decision.
總之就是這樣了
Is that why
所以…
you made that decision?
所以妳才會這樣決定嗎
Don't sulk.
不要哭喪著臉啦
My dream does not end here.
我的夢想還沒有結束
I lost to Orfevre in the year before last year.
上上次的有馬紀念輸給了”暴君”
Last year, I lost to Gentildonna.
上次則是輸給了”貴夫人”
I will win this year's Arima Kinen and get seven wins in G1.
我會贏下今年的有馬紀念 成為GI7勝
That is the perfect ending for me.
也就是美好的結尾
Gold...
黃金船…
Are you crying because it'll be my last match?
妳在為我的最後一賽哭泣嗎
No, because...
因為…
Because I have to win
黃金船的最後一場比賽
in your last match and you won't have your perfect ending.
會因為我的獲勝而無法 成為美好的結尾啊
You little...
妳這個傢伙
You think you'll win?
別開玩笑了
Brace yourself for a rude awakening, rookie.
覺悟吧 妳這個臭屁學妹
Don't go easy on me in my last race,
可別在我的最後比賽中放水喔
you genius.
這個進步神速的傢伙
You too, Gold.
黃金船也是
You will leave the gate safely, all right?
要好好衝出閘門喔
Is that provocation I hear?
這種大逆不道的話 是從這張嘴巴說出來的嗎
To Diamond's second victory.
那麼 敬光鑽的第二場勝利
Cheers!
乾杯…
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR SECOND VICTORY, DIAMOND
(賀 光鑽取得第二勝)
I hope my victory today will make you run faster tomorrow, Kita.
希望今天的勝利 能成為明天小北的動力呢
Yes, yes.
我懂…
I am feeling very confident and motivated now.
我收到了很多勇氣和激勵呢
"ARIMA KINEN, NAKAYAMA RACECOURSE" Here we are.
(有馬紀念 中山競馬場) 終於到了呢
We have arrived at Arima Kinen!
有馬紀念終於到了
Kita?
小北
I wonder what it's like
不知道跑最後一賽…
to run your last race.
會是種什麼樣的心情呢
I don't know.
我不知道
But we shouldn't dwell on it.
不過 我認為現在也不用去懂
We can only focus on our current race.
因為我們只能拼盡全力 在眼前的比賽中奔跑啊
Diamond...
光鑽…
Don't you want to give Gold a proper farewell?
妳不是要送黃金船一程嗎
Do your best tomorrow.
要加油喔
I will win the race.
我一定會贏的
Despite the harsh winter,
在這冬季寒風吹過的中山競馬場
120,000 passionate fans have gathered at the Nakayama Racecourse.
今年來了12萬名的粉絲
The cold failed to extinguish the flame in their hearts.
連十二月寒風 也吹不熄的這份熱烈期待
The race will begin soon.
終於要開始了
The end of G1, Arima Kinen.
總結算 GI有馬紀念
Let's welcome our commentator, Mr. Yamamoto.
再次有請解說員山本先生
We do have a star-studded lineup, don't we?
這次的參賽陣容很豪華呢
Yes, we do.
是啊
We have Bravo Day, two wins in G1, voted second place by the fans.
有GI兩勝 粉絲投票第二名的讚嘆之日
We have the champion of Kikuka Sho, Kitasan Black.
今年的菊花賞冠軍 北部玄駒
We have the very promising candidate from this autumn, Sounds of Earth.
從秋季開始就狀況絕佳的萬籟爭鳴
River Light and her rival sister, Parol.
光明河流與帕洛爾的姊妹對決 也很令人期待
And of course, the fan-voted first place,
但最大的看點就是粉絲投票第一名
also her last race in the Twinkle Series, Gold Ship.
將這次比賽當成閃光系列賽 的最後一賽的黃金船了
Good luck, Gold Ship!
看妳的了 黃金船
Go, Earth!
加油 萬籟
You can do this, Earth!
衝啊 萬籟
The weather is cold but the atmosphere here is warm.
明明這麼冷卻熱情如火
I'm so nervous but also excited.
明明害怕卻如此興奮
This must be Arima Kinen.
這就是有馬紀念
I am now
我現在…
on the stage called Arima Kinen.
就站在有馬紀念的舞台上
G1, ARIMA KINEN NAKAYAMA, 2,500M COURSE
(GI 有馬紀念) (中山 草地2500公尺)
All horse girls are in the starting stalls.
好的 所有賽馬娘已就閘門位置
The last grand prix of this year,
年末的大獎賽
Arima Kinen.
有馬紀念
Everyone is off to a good start.
所有人都漂亮起跑了
Good!
好
Everyone is fighting for the first spot now.
現在各方都在爭奪首位
Kitasan Black is in the lead.
由北部玄駒取得領先
Opheryu is on the inside line.
在內側的是巨星俳優
Sounds of Earth is following closely behind.
萬籟爭鳴就緊跟其後
As usual, Gold Ship occupies the last spot.
黃金船如同往常在最後一名
All 16 horses are heading to the first straight.
16名選手現在要進入第一個直線
Go, Earth!
衝啊 萬籟
Win this G1!
把GI贏回來
Do we cheer for Gold Ship or Kitasan?
到底是要幫黃金船 還是北部加油才好啦
Both!
當然是兩邊都要啊
All the best, Kita.
加油啊 小北
-Gold Ship... -Gold Ship's last race, eh?
-黃金船的… -黃金船的最後一賽嗎
Arima Kinen,
夢幻的大獎賽
the birthplace of many memorable moments.
這個有馬紀念 是誕生許多名場面的著名舞台
Symboli Rudolf was here.
出現過現役最強的魯道夫象徵
The legend, Manhattan Cafe, was here.
以及完成世代交替的曼哈頓咖啡
Who are you?
你是誰啊
Not to mention Oguri Cap, who made
還有在閃光系列賽中完成最後一賽
her final comeback in her last match of the Twinkle Series.
又驚人復活的小栗帽
Who are you again?
妳又是誰
This is exciting.
果然還是令人期待呢
Gold Ship has the same colour. Will she make a similar comeback?
那擁有相同毛色的賽馬娘 黃金船的復活
Do you want some?
要喝嗎
Kitasan Black maintains her lead.
北部玄駒掌握了主導權
They passed the first bend amidst the loud cheer.
在呼聲中通過了第一彎道
Behind her was No. 12, Parol.
接著是12號帕洛爾
No. 7, Opheryu is on the inside line.
內側是7號巨星俳優
No. 9, Sounds of Earth is on the outside.
從外側看去是9號萬籟爭鳴
Then, No. 4, Bravo Day.
接下來是4號讚嘆之日
No. 5, Great House.
5號雄偉之屋
Behind them is No. 2 Brave Target.
接著後面是2號勇氣之星
I can feel the pressure from the veterans.
我感受到了 前輩們的壓力
They are now on the second bend and the straight.
通過第二彎道 來到了非終點直線
All horses are in a single file now.
隊伍現在成為一列縱隊
No. 11, Kitasan Black, still has the lead.
領先的還是沒變 依然是11號的北部玄駒
Then, it's No. 12, Parol.
接著是12號帕洛爾
What?
居然
-Here she goes! -A white shadow.
-她出手了 -白色鬃毛有了動作
Gold Ship is on the move!
黃金船出手了
She overtakes everyone.
不停地超越
She overtakes one after another.
不停地從外側超越了眾人
-Is this it? -Is Gold Ship doing it?
-要出手… -要出手了嗎 黃金船
This long sprint...
那個長距離衝刺
River Light is heading to the fourth bend.
光明河流進入第四彎道
Sounds of Earth is following behind.
接著是萬籟爭鳴
Opheryu closes the gap too.
內側的巨星俳優也衝上來了
-Go, Earth! -Opheryu closes the gap too.
-好 衝啊 萬籟 -內側的巨星俳優也衝上來了
The final stretch.
來到最後的直線了
Kitasan Black is in the lead.
領先的是北部玄駒
Kitasan Black!
是北部玄駒
Kita, go!
加油 小北
200 meters left. Keep up.
剩下200公尺 撐下去
You can do this!
加油
Kitasan Black is accelerating.
北部玄駒持續加速
River Light catches up to her.
光明河流追上她了
But Gold Ship is coming.
但就在這個時候 黃金船
Gold Ship is approaching.
黃金船來了
Gold Ship is back.
黃金船復活了
Show us how you overtake everyone again!
再讓我們看一次那個大超車吧
Go, Gold Ship!
衝啊 黃金船
You can do this!
拜託妳 衝下去啊
Run with everything you have.
用盡妳最後的力量
The unsinkable ship, Gold Ship.
不沉之船 黃金船
In her final race,
她的最後一賽
will she sail
這艘冠有黃金之名的船
to victory?
她會航向名為勝利的終點嗎
She can't!
但是沒能追上去
She can't close the gap.
黃金船沒能追上去
Kitasan Black takes the lead.
從前方開始是北部玄駒
Then, River Light.
光明河流
Then, No. 7, Opheryu.
然後是7號巨星俳優
Kitasan Black does not concede.
北部玄駒繼續領先
So close. So close.
還差一點…
Opheryu is here.
在這時巨星俳優衝出來了
Opheryu!
是巨星俳優
Sounds of Earth is here too.
萬籟爭鳴也追上來了
Opheryu secures the first spot
巨星俳優以首位之姿
and crosses the finishing line!
衝過終點
Opheryu won!
巨星俳優贏下了這座夢幻舞台
Yay!
太好了
Sounds of Earth is in the second place.
第二名是萬籟爭鳴
Such a mesmerizing concerto!
這是最棒的協奏曲了
Good job!
第二名辛苦了
The champion of Kikuka Sho, Kitasan Black, is in third place.
菊花賞的冠軍賽馬娘 北部玄駒是第三名
The top fan-voted athlete, Gold Ship,
人氣投票第一名的黃金船
finishes her last race in the eighth place.
她的最後一賽以第八名告終
What happened?
怎麼啦
Shouldn't you win in my last race?
不是要在我的最後比賽中 贏下勝利嗎
Gold...
黃金船…
I told you not to cry.
就跟妳說了 不要哭喪著臉啦
You did very well.
妳跑得很棒
Good job.
辛苦了
Thank you for this thrilling last race.
謝謝妳在最後還帶給我們 這種緊張的比賽
Six victories in G1!
GI6勝
That's impressive, Gold Ship.
是個很棒的成績喔 黃金船
It doesn't end here.
還沒結束呢
Wait for me, Orfevre, Gentildonna.
等著我吧 暴君與貴婦人
The loss I have in your hands in the Twinkle Series
在閃光系列賽的這筆帳
will be redeemed in Dream Trophy.
我一定會在夢之杯聯賽討回來的
My dream doesn't end here.
我的夢想不會結束
I will show everyone.
我會讓所有人看到的
You will face them again?
那個對決會再度上演嗎
The ship will continue to sail.
黃金的航行還沒有結束
Gold Ship!
黃金船…
-Wow. -Gold Ship!
-真是的 -黃金船…
-The 8th place outshines the 1st place.
-明明是第八名 卻比第一名還亮眼
-Indeed. -Gold Ship!
-就是啊 -黃金船…
-That's a very Gold Ship thing to do.
-真像是黃金船的作風
Gold Ship!
黃金船…
To my first Arima Kinen.
敬我第一次的有馬紀念
Cheers!
乾杯
NON-ALCOHOLIC BEER
(無酒精生啤酒)
You were so close, Kita.
太可惜了呢 小北
Getting third place in Arima Kinen is an achievement.
能在有馬紀念拿下第三名 已經很厲害了
Yes, you did very well.
是啊 妳表現得很精彩
Thank you.
謝謝大家
But...
但是…
I was hoping
果然還是很想贏呢
to win the race.
有馬紀念
Kita...
小北…
Gold?
黃金船
Here.
給妳
One side left for you.
妳只有一面
I have six sides to solve.
而我是六面
Can you solve it?
不曉得妳能轉出幾面呢
Is she...
難道說…
I will surpass you, Gold.
我會超越黃金船的
I'll solve all six sides
我會轉齊六面
and do better.
然後更上一層樓
My dream has just begun.
我的夢想才剛剛開始
In the upcoming year, I will...
在新的一年一定…
I must...
會更加地…
All right.
好
To my future.
敬未來的我
Cheers!
乾杯
Again?
又乾杯…